(The Flash:)You know why Batman
wanders around at night
(The Flash:)getting into fights?
(The Flash:)Scotch.
(Sheldon:)I am facing
a great deal of work.
(Sheldon:)And I do like things better when
famous people also like them.
(Howard:)Here.
(The Flash:)It's on the house.
(Sheldon:)The first one's free?
(Sheldon:)Flash, how do you
stay in business?
(The Flash:)You want to know my secret?
(The Flash:)I bought stock in Marvel.
(Amy:)Hi, Bert.
(Amy:)This is my friend, Penny.
(Howard:)Hi.
(Bert:)Hey, come on in.
(Bert:)I'll gonna go turn on
some rock music.
(Bert:)That's a geology joke.
(Amy:)Bert's a geologist.
(Bert:)And a joker.
(Penny:)How early are we?
(Amy:)Oh, actually,
we're an hour late.
(Penny:)I suddenly wish
Sheldon was here.